A Guide to the Berryman United Methodist Church (Richmond, Va.) Records, 1913-2003
Library of Virginia
- Young People's Dept. - Secretary's Book, 1932-1933. (Box 47, Folder 14)